Episode 19
- Dad, what are you doing?
- I was going to have a drink.
I'll drink with you. Did you and mom fight?
You guys are on the same side, why did you fight?
It's very hard to be on the same side.
It is good news to me.
it it good news to you?
I don't think peace is always the best.
conflicts force us to see things from a different point of view
If I hadn't fought with Hye Yoon,
we wouldn't have been able to understand each other as deeply.
Thats the best outcome of a fight. But every fight doesn't always end like that.
If things go wrong, two parties will part only leaving battle scars behind.
I would rather be a hypocrite than see you ruin yourself
I am no longer neutral.
How can he do this to me. How can he
Sis. Hye Yoon.
were are you?
- You surprised me.
- You weren't sleeping, right?
i was relieved to see that the light in your room wasn't turned off
I was going to sleep. What's wrong?
you said that you just got back from a trip.
Yeah, after we came back, we had dinner and was hanging out.
I wanted trotters we went out to eat and we thought of you so we brought trotter for you
Gosh. You're so full of energy. How did you live until now when you wanted to live like that?
Sister-in-law. Please come out. I set the table.
This late at night? I better call Hye Yoon too.
Unnie, come out quickly.
- You came?
- Who?
Uncle. I didn't wake you, did I?
- No, you didn't.
- Let's eat!
you both looks so happy
Trotter goes well with soju but you have work tomorrow so we bought soda.
You are more thoughtful than I thought you'd be.
He's a bit picky. Unexpected.
You were more easygoing that expected. Grabbing food without washing your hands.
Here they go again. How can they be more cheesy than a couple in their 20s?
We met late in life. Time seems so wasted.
I wish that time will stop.
Unnie, we are going to sleep here tonight.
- Is that alright, honey?
- Of course I go where you are.
- I am against it.
- Unnie!
I am sorry. I have caused strain in your relationship with mom.
No, you didn't. It's actually a good thing.
Both me and your mom are at a turning point in our lives.
It's easy to talk about it, but do you think it will be easy to live in the countryside?
Your mom has only lived in the city.
When the department store is her friend, when she agreed to live in the country side for me,
I wondered if it will really work.
It's good that it's out in the open now.
Mom's too immature. Like a kid playing with the fire. I can't be at ease.
You also speak about me like that when I am not around.
Do you guys know? How much I love you guys and gave all I got?
If you knew, you can't be like this to me.
Let's go in and sleep. Sis, leave my room alone. Don't rent it out.
So I could come and spend the night sometimes.
I won't rent it out but once Hye Yoon is married, they will live there.
- Then what about us?
- I'll give you my room when you come.
You're too much. You only like your daughters.
I wasn't going to say this but you really discriminated among Hye Jin, Hye Yoon, and me.
Look at this, how immature you are. Are you my kid?
It's not like that.
It hasn't been decided yet. If you don't like it, we could live in my room.
No, don't mind us and do as you wish.
Call Jung Hoon and ask him to meet us tomorrow.
Uncle will buy you something yummy to eat.
It's alright.
I insist also to congratulate on you guys getting back together. I need to get you a wedding gift.
- Let's pick one tomorrow.
- Hye Yoon, listen to what he says.
Great idea, Honey.. You're better than me.
- He really is better than you.
- Still my room is off limits.
- She's mine.
- I know, I was just trying to scare her.
- Yeah.
- What are you upto?
- I was about to do dishes.
- At this hour?
I had a drink with dad.
It's nice, between father and son. Uncle and aunt came over to my place now.
Uncle wants to meet tomorrow. He will buy us a wedding gift.
Tomorrow is your day off, right?
Yeah, uncle? Oh, Min Ho.
It's awkward calling him that.
I can't make it tomorrow. My mom and dad are not speaking to each other.
Mom is camped out in my room.
- Because of me?
- No.
Why would you think that? I think I have to stay home. I have to make my mom feel better.
Should I go?
You want to come to our house? What if you get more hurt from my mother?
I'm not going to get hurt. I'll just let it in one ear and out the other.
Do you think that is easy?
I'm going to try. You accepted my mom.
I want to do that.
Why are you quiet?
I am touched.
I am confident I could make you feel touched more when we live together.
What does your mother like?
Why aren't you sleeping?
Are you going to family court again?
I have to go.
You said that the family court is to help the divorce process.
- Yes.
- Helping is a good thing, right?
It's a good thing.
I got a good idea.
What?
He says the three of us should sleep together.
I have thought it over and I think mom and dad don't fight when I am around.
I'll help.
I will ask for the last time before we meet the mediators tomorrow.
- Are you really sure?
- It only hurts my lips to talk about it more.
Good for you. Once you decided to divorce, you don't waver.
At first I was a little hesitant.
You made me strong.
Because you hated me so much, I pushed you harder.
What's the point of having this talk? We will be at each other's throat tomorrow.
- You are that type of person.
- What if I am not?
If you let go of everything at tomorrows mediation,
maybe we could have another chance.
What if you are the same even when I let go of everything?
You have to be prepared to lose everything when you are let go of things.
That's love.
If we can start again,
only love would be able to do that.
This time, mediation is unable to reach settlement since the gap between both parties' requests is too vast and active assets have not been accounted for yet.
and the case will be transferred to the court once more.
Prove your case during trial and receive the verdict.
What is active asset?
The asset you currently own.
You're requested $4 million in division of assets and Mr. Nam Do Hyun offered $500,000.
The judge concluded the gap between both parties requested amount is too large, it can't be mediated.
So you should go to the trial and show the evidence in order to get a verdict.
You're very kind, lawyer.
I tend to be kind.
Good for you. I am tired of the trial yet you're studying the law.
Thank you. I became much more knowledgeable in law thanks to you.
This is only the beginning. Cheer up.
Who are you?
Since you said you're getting tired, I wanted to remind you who started this fight.
Even if I hadn't started, she would have started it first then.
If you are full of anger,
that must mean you're not over her yet. Then ask for her forgiveness.
Oh, this is my personal opinion. I am just saying it because you're Hye Yoon's brother-in-law.
I want to get to know you better. I want discount on my skin treatments too.
He won't ask for forgiveness. Also, there is no compromise for us.
The only thing that's left is who will win the war to get the most spoils.
After spending some time with the two sisters, I know they are very decisive. They are very clear in making and ending relationships.
I'll be going.
Why are you always drinking in the house?
- Why do you follow me?
- I didn't follow you. This is my house.
- What would Tae Won learn from watching you?
- I didn't even drink that much.
Are you going to accused me to be an alcoholic this time?
Stop it.
For a moment, I had my hopes up. It seemed like you were wavering last night so I thought maybe you will give up.
But as expected, you didn't give up.
Unless you give me the assurance, I cannot let go of everything.
I really can't stand you. How are you unwilling to do anything that might put you at a slightest disadvantage?
Why would I do something that will put me at a disadvantage. I won't do anything that will leave me stranded.
Great! You even had your money siphoned to uncle.
You were moving your money to that account. That's why you didn't have any cash with you.
Do you really want to be like that?
I guess you received response from your request to trace my finances
Now, you are very knowledgeable in legal terms.
Do you think you will be safe if you have your account under an alias?
I am safe. He won't give you the money.
He is now my uncle.
Relationships are not defined by documents (family relationships).
He and I, we have a history, times spent together.
We have spent time together and we also have a child.
But what happened to us?
I forgot to give this to you when you bought a cell phone last time.
Wedding date is near but why aren't you passing out wedding invitations?
Why are you so curious about that?
You know Mr. Ahn, the owner of the rice cake shop in the marketplace, his son had set the wedding date and everything, but the wedding was called off.
The bride said they will even pay for the lease on the apartment—
My daughter's wedding has been postponed. It wasn't called off.
It wasn't called off? I thought it was called off because you weren't passing the wedding invitation and you would changed the subject whenever I brought it up.
I want them to live with me. So they are trying to get a permission from his parents.
There is a saying if you even own the smallest plot of land, you don't let your son live with the wife's family.
When your future son-in-law comes from a well-to-do family, why would they allow him to live with you?
I guess you don't read the newspapers these days. It's trendy to live with the wife's family these days.
They say the wife needs have it easy for a peaceful family.
More and more people are living with the wife's family.
You really are a trend setter. Even your blue eye shadows, I am growing to like them.
Give me some too. The blue eye shadows. I want to give it a try.
Don't just try it on. Buy one. I will give you a 20% discount.
You're not eating?
Dad went out to get the sushi you like.
I think you really married well. You couldn't have asked for a better husband.
- Mom, just get over it.
- Don't treat me like a child.
Are you trying to make me feel better with a candy?
You don't make any sense. Who's treating you like a kid?
You were, the whole time. Why don't you take my words seriously?
I told you no to Hye Yoon. Did I just say no without a reason? I had my reasons.
Hye Yoon's mom is below normal. Hye Yoon is too opinionated and she has issues with insecurity.
Protect the weak and treat people with warmth and cheerfulness.
Don't let money be the most valuable thing in your life.
When you judge a person, do it based on his character. Don't be blinded by his backgrounds.
Even though you may lose out, don't do something that will upset someone.
Who said these things?
You. You taught me these things.
I grew up adding my values to your values.
But now you're telling me it's wrong.
You say I have to marry a girl with a similar family background.
You tell me heart follows money.
You say you're in a different class from Hye Yoon's mom.
The day Hye Yoon told you that we broke up,
she wanted to make it crystal clear to you that we didn't break up because of you.
Because she didn't want to make you to be an ignorant parent who made her son break up because you were against the marriage.
And she also worried about how she would explain it to others.
Who are you exactly? Which one is the real you?
Get out.
You are at loss for words too right? After hearing what you said in a connected matter like that. How do you think I feel? I am going through a mental breakdown.
- Don't go on.
- I won't.
At least come downstairs to eat. You are weak. Don't get sick after getting stressing over things.
When you get sick, dad and I have to suffer because of it.
I said get out!
- Did you bring them?
- Yes, I did.
I am not sure if it will fit on you though.
Even if I have to twist my body around, I have to make body fit into your clothes.
The way how you're dressed now, it looks fine.
- Is it fine?
- Yes, just wear your clothes. It's better.
I am nervous. I met her last time and she was a force to be reckoned.
If you're like this from the first step, it will be hard for you.
In the process of preparing for the wedding, the easiest step was meeting the parents.
- It doesn't seem real.
- It is real. Accept it.
I understand. Teacher Jung, who went through two break-ups while preparing for the wedding.
Don't people recognize you on the streets these days?
No. Why do you ask?
Your footage I uploaded on youtube, It's very popular, your couple is known as the "yogang couple".
I might make it big thanks to you.
Fine, if you could step over me to succeed, please do so.
In return, make sure to give lots of gift money for our weeding.
- You're here.
- I am not late, am I?
- No.
- How are my clothes?
- Who asked you to dress in unstylish clothes?
- These are not stylish?
Yes. It screams I am on a blind date for marriage.
Let's go.
You've met her before.
I did.
- Hello, Mother(-in-law).
- Yes, sit down.
I am not late.
I know. I was early.
We were having salads. Order something.
- I am alright.
- What do you mean alright. You're a piggy.
Wait a little. I will order a pizza.
It's alright. Don't leave.
Stay by my side.
I was curious about this. Why did you date him even becoming a fool about it?
Is it because my son is from a rich family?
- Because he's good looking?
- You're questions are too vulgar.
I didn't know I was becoming a fool. I wanted to give in to him and give him many things.
You agreed to sign the pre nup.
You know that he won't give you a penny if you divorce.
Yes.
I heard you are estranged from your family. Do you have a personality problem?
That suits our family well. Think about your personality, mom.
Right. Let's not talk about personalities.
The two of us will plan and have the wedding.
Getting married twice in one year is a bit too much.
You and father don't like her all that much. To avoid hassle,
let's not make it into a family event.
Fine. We don't know when you might get divorced, we don't need to invite people to announce your wedding.
- However, is that alright with you?
- Yes.
Even if you're estranged from your family, your parents are okay with that?
Even though from outside, it might look like you married into a prestigious family. But in reality, you are not gaining anything.
- Yes.
- Is it alright to not have a meeting between the parents before the wedding?
Yes, Mother. My family owns a well known corporation too.
But I don't like my family. I was hurt by them a lot.
Hey! Why are you telling me your story when I am not even prepared?
- I can't?
- No, you can't.
Don't overflow me with the emotions that is beyond my capacity.
I still don't have any intention to like you.
Thus, don't say things that might make me like you.
Out of the things I said earlier, what might make you like me?
Why do you want to know that?
So I could keep doing it.
So there was a reason why my son liked you.
It seems like you guys are hitting it off. More so that I expected. I was watching because it's interesting.
It's not such a great thing to hit it off with me. That means she is too sharp and twisted.
It seems like you know yourself too well.
Also, I like it that you don't use corny phrases.
I am not corny. It's a wedding after all. Are you sure I don't have to do anything?
I could buy you something.
You don't have to buy us anything, These days, I am having fun making him pay for things.
You taught me that. A man opens his wallet for a woman he likes.
These days, I don't spend money.
Where did you find her?
I have to get going. If there is more things to discuss, do it among yourselves.
Your mother isn't as scary as I thought.
- Do you think you could handle her?
- Yes. I think I could handle being the daughter-in-law.
Yes, Mother.
You are not with Ki Joong still. Are you?
- No.
- Go to Ki Joong's apartment. I will be there.
You know the pass code, right? I don't.
I know. I will be there and wait for you.
Did you have something to say to me?
Move away from me. I might raise my hand.
You might get hit if you are near.
Sit!
You don't like your family?
You were hurt by your family?
You want to join my family?
You want to marry my son?
Aren't you out of your mind?
My Ki Joong needs to marry someone who was loved by her parents and has a positive attitude and someone who's sound in mind and body.
Not someone like you who's dark, hurt and complicated.
How dare you!
Why aren't you saying anything? Earlier, you talked back to everything I said.
Are you scared since Ki Joong is not around?
I am shocked.
Of course if I remember our first meeting, your behavior isn't surprising.
- Earlier, you were.
- That's because Ki Joong was there.
I know my son well and he has a strong personality.
If I am against this marriage, he will even cut off ties with his parents.
I am scared of my son.
Then, in the future, do you plan to be nice when Ki Joong is around and call me afterwards like this?
You're not a dumb one. Yes, that's the plan.
Get lost. Stay away from Ki Joong!
- I don't want to do that.
- What?
I am going to endure him. I don't want to lose him.
I've lost him once already. I don't want to lose him again.
I just need to avoid being alone with you.
If our conversation is off the record, I am not going to just take it.
Well scares me is that Ki Joong finding out how I treat his mother.
I am not scared of you.
- I will get going.
- I knew you will be this type of bi***.
If you weren't too much, why would you be estranged from your famliy?
Man, love. How long do you think that will last?
Even though it may not last long, it seems like he's definitely mine for now.
- Seeing you furious like this!
- This insolent bi***.
Shut up!
How about your Father?
I bought sushi and brought it. Are you still going to punish me like this?
You think our relationship succeeded because you tried hard.
I tried as much as you did.
- I know.
- What do you know?
You knew, yet you couldn't even stay neutral and choose to be a hypocrite?
What makes me mad is that you and our son, the two people most important to me is unable to understand me.
I was against Hye Yoon marrying our son. Why is that a senseless thing to do?
Are they normal? Why won't you believe my words when I said her mother ran a background check on our family?
Just because I think differently from you, you think I am abnormal?
You must believe me at all times.
That's the reality of your love towards me when I loved you all my life.
I tremble from this sense of betrayal.
Your father must have come downstairs.
Hello, Mother.
Before, you never came unless I asked you to.
Now you visit even when I don't ask.
- Have fun. I won't be here.
- Where are you going? It's cold out.
Where ever I may go, it won't be colder than this house.
- Stop it already.
- Stop what?
This is who I am. Double faced, only care about my son, selfish towards my family.
- Father.
- Hello.
- Share this.
- How about you?
- I will take care of myself
- I am making rice.
It's alright. Have fun.
You come out often lately.
Sis, do you want to go on a trip together?
- Do you want to?
- I want to leave home for couple days.
But as you know, I don't have friends.
I only appear to be friendly.
I don't have anyone I could go on a trip with.
Then go by yourself. I can't because of Ki Joong.
Did you set the wedding date?
That girl, Dong Bi or something, I just can't stand her.
I thought it was weird when you said you'll give them your permission.
I won't go anywhere until I remove that girl from Ki Joong's side.
Her father is well known businessman in Busan.
I won't let him marry a family that runs a company.
I will have him marry a family of scholars, government officials, or artists.
What's most important is the person. Just because she was brought up in such family doesn't mean she will be a good person.
Here you go with your righteous talk. You take care of your things first. What are you going to do about Jung Hoon?
His marriage is not the issue here. I feel like my whole life has been betrayed by my husband.
Is there anything you want to eat? Rather, is there anything you want to have?
I will buy it for you.
You're happy. To see me miserable.
Please enjoy, Father.
I am sorry for behaving based on my mood and without taking you into consideration.
No, that just means you're that comfortable with me. It's alright with me.
- Mom probably went to aunt's house.
- I know.
Let's eat.
I am sorry. For causing trouble.
No, I am relieved that me and my wife is able to realize there are issues that needs to be dealt with in our relationship.
We could resolve them. Don't worry too much.
Yes.
Gong Ki Ddol.
How have you been, Aunt?
I see you often lately.
I asked her to come here because your restaurant's food tastes the best.
I am honored. Just tell what you'd like to eat. It's my treat.
- Try to be this affectionate towards to me too.
- I understand, Madam Park.
What is it you'd like? You've nice lately, so I will grant one wish.
You.
That can't be done.
- I shouldn't have come.
-That's not true.
I thought it will work out if I put in the effort, but I am stuck from the beginning.
Do you think we could get married at this rate? Should we postpone it?
Don't postpone it. If postponing it made a difference, I would have postponed it. But it won't make a difference.
Let's just push through.
- Let's live in your mother's house.
- Really?
Iv'e given it some thought and realistically speaking, that's the best option.
It's better to not make a debt. We have to pay your loan too. Interest is accruing on that.
Do you think you could live with my mom? Even I don't get along with her sometimes and fight with her.
Then I will fight too. Who will you side with?
Of course your side.
Hey kids. I am going out.
With you moving about in an apron seems to make this house brighter.
- Thank you, Father.
- Thank YOU for making an effort.
I was worried you might never come to my house again.
- I like you, Father.
- I like you too.
- Stay longer.
- Yes, bye.
Bye, Dad.
Let's go out. Even if we stay at home, nothing will improve.
- To where?
- To prepare for the wedding, this and that.
Do we really not need to discuss it with your mother?
Even if it pains me, I am destined to gain independence from my parents.
Before we meet your mother, let's discuss some things first.
To be honest, living together may seem simple, but it's a difficult thing to do.
I thought the same.
It's easier for me since she's my mom but it's unfamiliar to you. My house is small too.
It will be really uncomfortable for you.
To hear you speak like that, I really feel like it will be alright for me to live with your mom.
I will be considerate so it wouldn't be difficult for you.
I could handle my mom.
You seem trustworthy.
Once I changed my way of thinking, my perspective changed,
and once my perspective changed, what I previously thought was difficult seems easy now.
- Wonderful!
- It feels nice to be praised.
Then, let's talk about how I should live with the in-laws.
Let's.
Mom, you don't have a towel?
What is this?
I drink it sometimes.
What are you doing, mom?
Mom, there is no more. I just drank for a short while because I was going through a hard time.
Do you think I haven't done this?
You want to rely on it when things are hard. I know.
But still, this isn't the solution.
Tae Won knew about it.
During the psychiatric evaluation, they asked him to draw the family,
he drew a picture of him watching me and his dad fighting.
I want to die. When does this end? I don't see the end in sight.
It couldn't be mediated. We have to go back to the trial.
I feel like I will be finished before the trial is finished.
Do you think a person is finished so easily like that?
The trial will be over before you're over, so don't do this sort of thing.
Who are you doing this for?
I try not to, but whenever I see my husband's face, I feel like I am going insane. I don't want to see him anymore.
But he keeps coming home.
You have a mom but why did you become friends with the alcohol instead?
Am I worse than alcohol?
You were really upset about Hye Yoon.
I didn't want to add to your troubles, so it was difficult for me to come clean to you.
I didn't want to be a burden to you anymore either.
I told you already. I like it when you are a burden to me. That makes me feel needed by you.
There is nothing sadder to hear as a parent than the child saying "I don't need you anymore".
Just between the two of us, I like you more than Hye Yoon.
Mom.
You don't know well because you only have one child.
You don't love all your children the same.
You have your favorites.
You're my favorite.
That doesn't really make me feel better.
It seems like you're saying I feel more sorry for you.
I found my husband's alias bank account, it's Uncle.
Alias account?
Tae Won's dad was siphoning money into Uncle's bank account.
Most of his cash assets were in that account.
So you're saying Braised Tofu was an accomplice in siphoning money away?
They are very close.
This is before he married aunt.
And mom, how can you call him Braise Tofu? Uncle will be disappointed to hear that.
That's why I try not to address him. I don't know how to address him.
When he walks about at home, I feel like there is a big black pig moving about and it startles me.
When you're like that, how will you live with Jung Hoon?
He's long, but he's not wide.
He has a small and cute face.
Braised Tofu has a big rectangular face.
Mom.
Laugh like that. I don't remember the last time I saw you laughing.
Do you think aunt won't like it if I ask her to give me the money my husband kept in uncle's alias account?
What is there not to like? Even if she's not willing to, we have to make her do it.
- Sis, we are here.
- We come everyday.
Why did you call us here? My room is not up for discussion.
I understand. I will leave it alone. I could just ask them to use Hye Yoon's room.
I guess you don't have much work. You seem to have a lot of free time.
Since he manages his building, he stays home most of the time.
Good for you. To be able to make a living like that.
I was born with lucky when it comes to money.
Whatever businesses I try, they usually don't fail,
once money comes into my pocket, I don't throw it away.
- Now I got to know you better, I realize you are actually quite a show off.
- A little bit.
- But when he shows off, it's not that unpleasant.
- Never mind.
How much do you like my Deul Rae?
Why do you ask?
As her older sister, I am checking how far you will go for Deul Rae.
Can you do anything for her?
Well, anything is a bit of stretch. Still I will do whatever I can.
I heard that you handle the alias bank account of my dog of son-in-law.
Did you manage the account even though you knew he was doing this to deceive my Hye Jin?
- No, Sis. He won't do such things.
- I didn't know.
- I thought I was managing slush fund for his clinic.
- See?
Then, since you found out. What will you do?
What about?
What do you mean what? You know that part of that money belong to Hye Jin.
- Then what should you do? You have to return it to her.
- I can't do that.
- Why can't you?
- Right, why can't you?
I can't do whatever I want. I have to ask Do Hyun.
You're the older one, you can't even do that when you're older?
- Are you his crony?
- No, I am not his crony. He and I are like sworn brothers who made a pact in the peach blossom orchard.
Then Hye Jin is your niece-in-law. She's your family.
Family or friend, who comes first?
Do I have to choose one?
We need to live together. Together.
What is this bullcrap?
If everyone were to live together, my kid will die. How can everyone survive together?
You have to choose one.
What will you do? Is it my kid or that dog of a son-in-law?
No one will die, Older sis. I mean Sister-in-law.
Your allotted share will just decrease.
If her share decreases, she doesn't even have a plan to make a living. That means she will die.
That dog of son-in-law is competent. Even after he gives her money, he could make more money in the future.
She's right, honey.
My Hye Jin lived as a housewife for 7 years.
She has to start with a new choice of career.
You're good with your words for a change. Right, you're an aunt indeed.
I still can't. I only lent him my name and it's not my money.
How can I give you the money without the owner's permission when the money doesn't belong to me?
It's under your name. Even if you were to take that money, he can't say anything. You can't be legally liable.
- You know so many things.
- I hear that often lately.
So you will do it?
- I can't.
- Why not?
I can't do it if I think about Do Hyun.
You can't do it if you think about Do Hyun, but you must do it if you think about Hye Jin.
I don't know about that.
You could leave. I don't want to deal with someone who doesn't even know what's important in life.
Sis!
Sis! How can you go into your room like that?
- What do you mean?
- You have to talk him into it.
You copied that bastard when you said, "Do I have to choose"? Right?
Yeah. Don't call him bastard.
He is no good. I should've found out earlier.
My husband did that too. He cared more about his friends than his family.
It will be you who suffers more from it.
I thought you got a great husband, but you didn't.
We all should cooperate.
I understand him.
I didn't say we shouldn't cooperate. We all should cooperate, not just one.
If you leave him like this, you are going to suffer forever.
Why?
He doesn't know what's important.
The most important thing is family and friends.
But he thinks that his family and friends are on the same level.
If you and Do Hyun fall into water, Min Ho will hesitate on deciding who to save and you will drown.
-He can't swim.
- That's what I'm talking about.
Be the first one to teach him using this oportunity.
Otherwise, you will be treated the same as Do Hyun.
How is she? Is she mad?
-No, I'm mad.
-Why?
Did you have to marginalize me in front of her?
When did I do that?
Do I come first or Do Hyun?
Don't say, "We should all coexist with each other".
Who comes first?
You can't compare humans.
Do Hyun is Do Hyun and you are you.
You are my Dul Rae.
I don't want to be your Dul Rae. Lets go home.
Are we not going to have dinner here?
My sister makes you dinner and lives with you!
Why do I have to do to be treated like him?
Choose one. I've never said it before.
Why? Because I love you.
I wanted to do everything you want.
But only I was trying.
You never did a single thing for me, only for me.
I sold my bike.
Right, you sold that. You have an excellent memory.
I had forgotten about how I bought your bike back.
I guess you remember everything you buy for me.
Does her words make sense?
Oppa, it's almost 3 pm. You said you have to go to the clinic.
- Are you tired?
- I am alright.
- When will you get a divorce?
- After the trial is over.
Your wife should just agree to a settlement. Why does she go through a trial?
Why do you want to raise your kid?
He's my kid and I want to raise him. What's wrong with that?
It's better for him to be raised by his mom.
After my parents were divorced, I lived with my mom and also with my dad.
It was better when I lived with my mom.
- Your parents are divorced?
- Yes.
I grew up with my grandmother. After my mom remarried.
You had a difficult childhood.
Whenever I tell people that I lived with my grandmother after my parent's divorce,
they always feel awfully sorry for me.
- You weren't?
- No, it was quite alright. I had a dream too.
I wanted to become an actress. I became a racing model (models to pose in front of cars) to make a living.
People told me if it pans out well, I will be able to become an actress. So I tried this and that.
It was very hard to make it. I even had a small role in a drama.
- I didn't have many lines though.
- Is that right?
- I am not a bimbo.
- Did I say you were?
You keep on treating me like a dumb person. It makes me feel bad.
I need to get going.
- Why do you go back and forth?
- About what?
Did you think I wouldn't know? Why do you keep comparing Hye Jin and me?
She said she won't live with you. Then you should come to me. Why do you keep wavering between us two?
- Do you want to live with me?
- Yes, I want to live with you.
- Why?
- I think we're a good match.
In what way? In blood type?
See, you're treating me like a bimbo again.
- Do you know how accurate blood types are?
- Fine.
- Are you coming tonight?
- Well.
Come. I will be waiting. I will make you the sweet and sour pork I learned from yesterday's cooking class.
Why?
- This will do.
- What do you mean?
Life is quite funny.
How did you end up meeting and end up like this?
I didn't have any intention to break my family apart.
I was planning to have some fun with you and end it afterwards.
But, it seems like the outcome will be the opposite of that.
Do you know why? Because I really wanted you.
I wanted you with the all the energy in the universe.
I didn't want to be abandoned.
Open the door. Why do you lock the door?
- I want to be alone.
- Why do you want to be alone?
Let's have a talk. Let's have a talk.
I can't get used to your being like this. You're a "Like Girl".
You said you like everything.
I liked everything, but how about you? Did I really like everything because I actually liked it?
While loving you, I threw away many of my habits and way of thinking.
What did you throw out while loving me? I am not talking about an item.
There is nothing, right? You're the same. You insist on being fair and refusing to choose.
- But you don't have a priority.
- Why is having a priority necessary?
I am your wife. You're my husband.
It's necessary once you have a family.
I lost many things while loving you.
What did you lose while loving me? You have it all.
The alias account. Did you have to say no about it so clear cut like that?
You could have said I will think about it. I will try to persuade him. There were many things you could have said.
Only your opinions matter to you. You say co-exist in words but you only insist on your opinions.
You just say what you have to say. Let me say something too.
She locked it again.
We are having our first fight.
I guess this is how couples fight.
Why are you here in the morning?
I am about to die.
You were dying of happiness just then.
You're already bored?
I am about to die because of you.
Take the money in my account.
My sister-in-law found out about it and told me to give her half of the money.
Listen to her. She doesn't make any sense. Why is she asking you for the money? It's my money.
That's why I told them I can't do that. It's your money.
She said it's the alias account under my name. I could use it as I see fit.
- Ignore them.
- I was planning to ignore them. But my wife,
my wife is throwing a fit. She locked the master bedroom and won't unlock it from yesterday.
Telling me I don't have my priorities and that I need to listen to my sister-in-law.
I am your wife's uncle now.
I really can't stand those women. They don't have any conscience.
I will talk to my wife.
Talking won't solve the problem. Do a proper job of dividing assets.
Do Hyun, I want to keep my family. Please, save me.
Oh, I am tired.
Going back and forth.
Why did I give birth to kids to go through this suffering?
I thought it would be over once I marry them off.
One needs continuous maintenance. The other I will have to live with them after her marriage.
I am happy even thinking about that. I will live with that woman's son and shove it to her face.
They told us they are coming so I better start cooking.
Did you lose your phone?
No.
I called you many times but you didn't pick up.
What do you mean why? You didn't answer my phone on purpose?
I was a bit busy. You really changed. You didn't care about those things before.
I know.
- What is this?
- Prenuptial agreement.
I called to get your signature on this.
Let's just get married soon.
What are you doing?
Marriage, let's forget about it.
Why?
I am not confident.
You were more than confident until yesterday.
Did something happen?
I realized I am not the marrying type.
- Can you please leave?
- Why are you acting like this?
Don't ask me why. Just leave. Please.
Let's make this clear. Are you just saying no to marriage or you want out of this relationship too?
I didn't think about that yet. What I want right now is for you to leave my space.
Should I open the door for you?
No. I will open it myself.
Tell me once you're done thinking.
Are you still with Aunt?
Aunt said she doesn't feel like going home today.
Did you meet Dong Bi?
I met her. Why? Are you going to give me a warning like last time?
Did you leave something behind?
I don't know what my mom said to you,
responding like this is not good.
What's not good about it? Could it get worse?
This involves you and me. You are making a unilateral decision.
I briefly forgot about this thing called family.
How my family tormented me, it all came back after meeting your Mother.
My father, dad, older sisters, my younger brother. I barely escaped them but I cannot enter the quagmire again for your sake.
You just need to consider me in marriage.
What if your mom torments me behind your back. Can you prevent that from happening?
I can't do anything about what happens when I am not looking.
You should be able to handle such things. You're an adult.
You're mom is too skilled and difficult for me to handle.
You get me in return.
I am worth that much.
I don't think there is a guy worth harming and damaging myself.
You taught me that. I risked everything for you. What happened afterwards?
If we talk about the past, we can't make any progress.
Your mother told me that you need to meet someone with a positive attitude and who's sound in mind and body.
She's right. Mom's know instinctively. If this is good or bad for my kid.
I am not taking a step back just because I am scared.
It's because what your mom said, they weren't completely wrong.
I want to meet a woman with a positive attitude with a sound mind and body.
However, I am not attracted to them.
My heart doesn't grow warm.
That's not pleasing to hear.
It sounds like you're attracted to me because I am sick and dark.
Please leave.
Mom.
- She's not here.
- Where did she go? I told her we're coming.
I guess she went somewhere briefly. It's still here.
Mom really likes that. She hugs it when she sleeps.
Really?
What are you looking at?
- Why are you doing that to Brownie?
- He reminds me of someone.
- You're here already?
- Where did you go?
I went out to get tofu. You said Jung Hoon is coming. I was going to make soybean stew with tofu for dinner.
- What is he doing here?
- You don't really like Brownie.
- Throw it out.
- No, this is really useful when I get angry.
Let's go out.
Mother-in-law. I will listen to what you say. I will move in here.
- Good idea. What did your mom say?
- She didn't say much.
I don't need to see it to know what happened. I am sure she was furious.
- How about your father?
- He said it's not easy to live with your wife's family.
Living is difficult if you think it's difficult but easy if you take it to be easy.
- Take the easy approach.
- I plan to.
However, in order for me to live here, I think we need to set up some rules.
What kind of rules?
Like how you said before, your personality is
a bit forthcoming. That's the expression you used.
I said that. I am forthcoming.
However, as the minority in gender and I am moving in trusting Hye Yoon alone,
I think we need to set up some rules to respect each other.
Look at him. He's not such a pushover either.
It's a good idea. I wanted to talk about that too.
If you move in here, will you pay for the living expense?
Before we discuss that, I will take care of my paycheck from now on.
- Fine, take it once you get married.
- I mean starting now.
Fine.
- Here.
- What's this?
I told you I used up all of your paycheck on living expenses.
Yeah.
This is the tax exempt savings account I made for Deul Rae.
I thought she will never get married.
You have to keep it for 10 years to make it tax exempt, so I never withdrew any money.
Deul Rae's wedding didn't cost much.
You could have that.
Thank you.
Look at you saying thank you after I give you money.
If we move in, how much should we give you for living expenses?
I didn't calculate the exact amount yet. But I still think you need to pay for the living expenses.
We will. We prefer that too.
We could pay and I don't want to live for free. It's different from when we weren't married yet.
No one will oppose if you pay a lot for living expense, so feel free to do so.
Another thing, who's going to cook?
You were thinking about taking all the benefits and planning to slave me around?
Do you want to take turns?
We haven't discussed about that yet.
I work too so it's unfair that I am the only one who cooks.
I understand.
Mom, because we live together doesn't mean we have to do all activities together, right?
You don't have to.
Are you afraid I will tag along when you guys go out?
Don't worry. Even if you ask me to tag along, I won't.
What will you do once you have a kid?
- About what?
- Who's going to take care of the kid?
I could take one year maternity leave.
After one year passes, then what?
You guys take care of it. It's your kid.
- When are you planning to have a kid?
- We haven't discussed it yet.
Then what kind of rules do you want to set?
Leaving me behind when you guys go out?
- Why are you guys this way?
- Mom, that.
- What?
- What you're doing now. "Why are you guys like that?" Don't do that.
Why not?
You're grouping Jung Hoon and me to scold. You could only scold me, not Jung Hoon.
Mom, there is a saying that the son-in-law is a guest for 100 years.
Oh, my. Is that so?
I could take and handle your scolding,
it's different for the son-in-law.
Am I doing the right thing? I dragged him in for a revenge, but it seems like I might be at the losing end.
Fine. Anything else?
Of course there is something else.
Hey! Make it into a book and bring it. So I could memorize it word to word.
I think I made a mistake somehow.
Trying to win against a kid, that's the beginning of my loss right there.
Don't you agree?
No matter how I see it, you're not very likable.
That woman just needs to come to her senses. She's about to have her son taken away and why isn't she calling?
It's been so long since I've been out like this.
Yeah. So why do you always stay home?
Whenever I ask you to come out, what were you thinking?
Is he calling?
What?
He's not calling.
Trying to comfort this fool, look at me being dragged to places yesterday and today.
How can he be like this?
- Give me another glass.
- You pour yourself.
What did you do to Min Ho? He came to my clinic.
Do you think I will listen to your wishes if you do that?
It's alright to not do according my wishes, but please leave.
Please make it so that I don't have to see your face.
Why do you hate me so?
Think about what you have done. Including what you're doing now.
That's why I don't want to give you even a penny.
Why do I have to give money to someone who hates me?
You're not giving me the money. It's my share.
It's the price for working like a slave in this house.
Leave Min Ho alone. Even if you bother him, you won't get anything in return.
Only Deul Rae will be in a difficult position.
No, I will ask aunt to keep persuading Min Ho.
Seeing how you care about Min Ho's difficulty. I want to do whatever it is that makes it difficult for you.
Doing this, I am becoming a monster like you.
I am changing. I am falling apart. I am becoming a worse person.
You must be happy. To see things going your way.
Aren't you eating? I am hungry. Let's fight after eating.
Live with Do Hyun.
It's really scary when she's so determined like this.
I didn't eat because you haven't eaten. I am hungry.
Eat by yourself. Don't worry about me.
How can I eat alone?
I am going to unlock the door, okay?
What is this? You were being disloyal and ate alone?
Are you alright?
I am sorry. It's because I suddenly opened the door.
Let's go to the doctor.
No, we have to go. Get on my back.
I am back.
- I am back.
- Oh, you're here.
- Mom's not home yet?
- No, she isn't.
- I will get the door.
- Fine.
Mom, did you drink?
I made her drink. Because she doesn't know how to drink, she's like this after five glasses of wine.
- You're here.
- Yes, Brother-in-law.
Thank you for bringing her home.
It's nothing. Then I will get going.
Ha Dong Geun, you bastard.
- Mom.
- It seems like I need to stay longer.
I think it will be fun. I need to watch the fight.
How can you not call me even once when I am out? You hypocrite.
Hey, hand her to me.
- Bye.
- Yes.
Release me.
What do you take me for?
It would be fun for me if I could stay longer.
- I am leaving. ,br> - Yes, bye.
No way.
- Are you serious?
- Yes, I am serious.
Please schedule an outpatient appointment for tomorrow.
What's wrong? Do I have a terminal disease?
- Deul Rae.
- Why?
It's been 5 weeks.
What 5 weeks?
You're 5 weeks pregnant!
- What? I am pregnant?
- Yes!
- No way!
-That impossible thing happened to us.
No, this can't be. How can a child be born to a father who doesn't have any priorities?
No, this can't be. Our kid and another kid got into a fight and fell into the water. Who will you rescue first?
You're persistent.
- You'e talking about priorities at a moment like this?
- Who's your priority?
Oh my.
December 31st, Central Bank transfer $5.6 million, transferred from Jang Min Ho.
Min Ho! How can you do this to me?